<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<item>
		<title>International shipping</title>
		<link>http://demo2.woothemes.com/wootique/?page_id=1611</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>wooteam</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo2.woothemes.com/wootique/?page_id=1611</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2>
Amazon.com gladly accepts orders from all around the globe. Available product lines, shipping rates and fees may vary depending on the delivery address for your order.

To see the shipping rate information specific to your order's destination, click the link for your region at the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_nodeid_596184_related?nodeId=596184#related">bottom of this page</a> under the heading "Related Topics."

There may be limitations on where and whether Amazon Marketplace sellers offering international shipping. For more information, visit our <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/?nodeId=537804">Buying from Outside the U.S.</a> Help page.

Read more about shipping to <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_nodeid_596184_protect?nodeId=468640">U.S. protectorates</a> or <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_nodeid_596184_apo?nodeId=773768">APO, FPO, or DPO addresses</a>.

Your packages may be subject to the customs fees and import duties of the country to which you have your order shipped. These charges are always the recipient's responsibility. For further details, read about <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_nodeid_596184_restrict2?nodeId=596184#restrict">Restrictions</a> (which apply to all international shipments) and<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_nodeid_596184_import2?nodeId=596184#import">Import Fees Deposits</a>.

<a name="restrict"></a>
<h2>Restrictions</h2>
The following items can be shipped to almost all destinations outside the U.S.:
<ul>
	<li>books*</li>
	<li>DVDs</li>
	<li>music</li>
	<li>VHS videos</li>
</ul>
Additionally, some products in the following categories:
<ul>
	<li>automotive, baby, clothing, consumer electronics, health and personal care, home and garden, industrial and scientific, jewelry, pet supplies, shoes, software, sporting goods, tools, toys, video games, and watches</li>
</ul>
can be shipped to the following countries:
<ul>
	<li><em>Australia, Austria, Bahrain, Belgium, Brazil, Bulgaria, Canada, Chile, China, Colombia, Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Hong Kong, Hungary, India, Indonesia, Ireland, Israel, Italy, Japan, Kuwait, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malaysia, Malta, Mexico, Monaco, Netherlands, New Zealand, Norway, Philippines, Portugal, Poland, Qatar, Romania, Saudi Arabia, Singapore, Slovakia, Slovenia, South Africa, South Korea, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Taiwan, Thailand, United Arab Emirates, United Kingdom</em></li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1611</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-01-25 09:14:32</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>0000-00-00 00:00:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>draft</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>